export const questions = [
    {
      question: 'What is "Hello" in Yoruba?',
      options: ["Pẹlẹ o", "Bawo ni", "Odabo", "Jọwọ"],
      correctAnswer: "Bawo ni",
      difficulty: "Easy"
    },
    {
      question: 'How do you say "Thank you" in Yoruba?',
      options: ["Jọwọ", "Pẹlẹ o", "Ẹ ṣeun", "Odabo"],
      correctAnswer: "Ẹ ṣeun",
      difficulty: "Easy"
    },
    {
      question: 'What is "Goodbye" in Yoruba?',
      options: ["Bawo ni", "Odabo", "Pẹlẹ o", "Ẹ ṣeun"],
      correctAnswer: "Odabo",
      difficulty: "Easy"
    },
    {
      question: 'How do you say "Please" in Yoruba?',
      options: ["Jọwọ", "Pẹlẹ o", "Odabo", "Ẹ ṣeun"],
      correctAnswer: "Jọwọ",
      difficulty: "Easy"
    },
    {
      question: 'What is "Yes" in Yoruba?',
      options: ["Bẹẹni", "Rara", "Jọwọ", "Odabo"],
      correctAnswer: "Bẹẹni",
      difficulty: "Easy"
    },
    {
      question: 'What is "No" in Yoruba?',
      options: ["Bẹẹni", "Rara", "Jọwọ", "Odabo"],
      correctAnswer: "Rara",
      difficulty: "Easy"
    },
    {
      question: 'How do you say "Excuse me" in Yoruba?',
      options: ["Ẹ jọwọ", "Pẹlẹ o", "Odabo", "Bawo ni"],
      correctAnswer: "Ẹ jọwọ",
      difficulty: "Medium"
    },
    {
      question: 'What is "Good morning" in Yoruba?',
      options: ["E kaaro", "E kaasan", "E kuurole", "E kaale"],
      correctAnswer: "E kaaro",
      difficulty: "Medium"
    },
    {
      question: 'How do you say "I love you" in Yoruba?',
      options: ["Mo fẹ́ràn rẹ", "Mo n fẹ́", "Mo fẹ́", "Mo fẹ́ran"],
      correctAnswer: "Mo fẹ́ràn rẹ",
      difficulty: "Hard"
    },
    {
      question: 'What is "Good afternoon" in Yoruba?',
      options: ["E kaaro", "E kaasan", "E kuurole", "E kaale"],
      correctAnswer: "E kaasan",
      difficulty: "Medium"
    },
    {
      question: 'How do you say "Good evening" in Yoruba?',
      options: ["E kaaro", "E kaasan", "E kuurole", "E kaale"],
      correctAnswer: "E kaale",
      difficulty: "Medium"
    },
    {
      question: 'What is "Good night" in Yoruba?',
      options: ["Odabo", "O daaro", "E kaale", "E kuurole"],
      correctAnswer: "O daaro",
      difficulty: "Medium"
    },
    {
      question: 'How do you say "Welcome" in Yoruba?',
      options: ["Ẹ ku abọ", "Ẹ ku ikale", "Ẹ ku isinmi", "Ẹ ku iṣẹ"],
      correctAnswer: "Ẹ ku abọ",
      difficulty: "Hard"
    },
    {
      question: 'What is "How are you?" in Yoruba?',
      options: ["Bawo ni", "Ṣe daadaa ni", "Ṣe o wa", "Ṣe o n lọ"],
      correctAnswer: "Bawo ni",
      difficulty: "Medium"
    },
    {
      question: 'How do you say "I am fine" in Yoruba?',
      options: ["Mo wa daadaa", "Mo n lọ", "Mo n bọ", "Mo n ṣiṣẹ"],
      correctAnswer: "Mo wa daadaa",
      difficulty: "Hard"
    },
    {
      question: 'What is "See you later" in Yoruba?',
      options: ["Ma a ri e laipe", "Ma a bo", "Ma a lọ", "Ma a wa"],
      correctAnswer: "Ma a ri e laipe",
      difficulty: "Hard"
    }
];